A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 1
  - Social Health and Welfare, 1914-1921; 901; 1 document case
    Considerations between 1914 and 1916 concerning a proposed program in this field. It was the officers' opinion in 1921 that general social work was outside the scope of the Foundation's program.
    - Program and Policy - Social Health and Welfare, 1914-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charter, Constitution, and By-Laws, 1913-1949; 902; 1 document case
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws, 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws, 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws, 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws - Copies, 1916-1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws - Reports - Ch-1 - Ch-3, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Ch-1 TBA: General Education Board, Comparative Statement; July 17, 1936
      Ch-2 TBA: The Charter of the Rockefeller Foundation; February 26, 1940
      Ch-3: The Rockefeller Foundation Constitution and By-Laws; 1913-1928
    - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws - Reports, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Members and Meetings, 1891-1957; 903; 2 document case
    Minutes, correspondence, memoranda and reports dealing with the organization of and policies affecting the Board of Trustees and the Executive Committee. Also included are annual lists of Board members, material concerning nominees and candidates for the Board and the voting of proxies by the Foundation and its trustees.
    - Members and Meetings - Executive, Trustees, etc., 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Members and Meetings - Executive, Trustees, etc., 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Members and Meetings - Executive, Trustees, etc., 1913-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Members and Meetings - Candidates, 1926-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Members and Meetings - Candidates, 1926-1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Members and Meetings - Dockets and Minutes, 1927-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Members and Meetings - Dockets and Minutes, 1927-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1917-1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1917-1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1942-1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee - Lists, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Members and Meetings - Proxies, 1919-1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Members and Meetings - Proxies, 1919-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Reports - Mem Pro-1 - Mem Pro-3, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Mem Pro-1 DR 728: Proxies votes at special meetings of Members; March 8, 1929
      Mem Pro-2 DR 729: Proxies votes at special meetings of Members; November 13, 1929
      Mem Pro-3 DR 729: Proxies votes at special meetings of Members; December 14, 1932
    - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Reports - Pro-4, May 20, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Pro-4 DR 731: Proxies voted at Special meetings of Members; November 13, 1949
    - Members and Meetings - Eliot, Charles W., 1913-1917 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Members and Meetings - Flexner, Simon, 1914-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Members and Meetings - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Members and Meetings - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1921-1925, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Members and Meetings - Gates, Frederick T., 1891-1930 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Members and Meetings - Greene, Jerome D., 1916-1917, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Members and Meetings - Hadley, Herbert S., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Members and Meetings - Hopkins, Ernest M., 1928-1942 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Members and Meetings - Judson, Harry Pratt, 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Members and Meetings - Murphy, Starr Jocelyn, 1917-1921 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Members and Meetings - Rockefeller, John D. III, 1949-1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Members and Meetings - White, William Allen, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Members and Meetings - Wilber, Ray Lyman, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Members and Meetings - Minutes re: Retirement of Members, 1927-1929, 1936, 1938, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Officers' Conferences, 1919-1974; 904; 12 document cases
    Minutes of officers' conferences from the New York and Paris offices of the Rockefeller Foundation, from the International Health Division, and the General Education Board.
    - Paris Office, 1926-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Paris Office, 1926-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Paris Office, 1926-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Paris Office, 1926-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - IHD Staff Conference - Paris Office, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Minutes of the Budget Committee, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Education Board - Officers Conferences, 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - General Education Board - Officers Conferences, 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Humanities - Staff Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Humanities - Staff Minutes, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Natural Sciences Division Conferences, 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - International Health Division - Staff Minutes, 1920-1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Officers Conferences, 1919-1928 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Officers Conferences - Appendix, 1919-1928 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Officers Conferences, January 1929-September 1929 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Officers Conferences, January 1929-September 1929 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Officers Conferences, October 1929-1931 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Officers Conferences, October 1929-1931 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Officers Conferences, October 1929-1931 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Officers Conferences, October 1929-1931 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Officers Conferences, 1931-Appendix (1-2) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Officers Conferences, 1931-Appendix (1-2) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Officers Conferences, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Officers Conferences, 1932 - Appendix (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Officers Conferences, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Officers Conferences, 1940-1948 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Officers Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Officers Conferences, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Officers Conferences, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Officers Conferences, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Officers Conferences, 1967-1970 (Part 1) (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Officers Conferences, 1970 (Part 2) - 1973 (Part 1) (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Officers Conferences, 1973 (Part 3) - 1974 (Part 2) (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Officers Conferences, 1973 (Part 3) - 1974 (Part 2) (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Officers Conferences, 1973 (Part 3) - 1974 (Part 2) (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Officers Conferences, 1973 (Part 3) - 1974 (Part 2) (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Officers' Diaries, 905
    Related Archival Materials note
    SEE: R.G. 12, Diaries
  - Medical Sciences, 1913-1954; 906; 2 document cases
    Correspondence, memoranda and reports relating to program and policy in this field. Includes files on legal medicine, nursing education, psychiatry, public health training, and sex research. The Medical Sciences Division existed from 1929 to 1951. It was replaced by the Medicine and Public Health Division in 1951.
    SEE ALSO: Series 920 Medicine and Public Health
    - Program and Policy - Minutes, 1913-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Minutes, 1913-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy, 1916-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy, 1916-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy, 1916-1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-1, 1927-1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Pro-1: Appropriations, Pledges, Authorizations and Estimates; 1927, 1928, 1929, 1931, 1932, 1933
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-1a, Pro-2 - Pro-4, 1928-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Pro-1a: Summary of Appropriations and Contingent Policy with Probable Year of Payment, Medical Sciences; 1941
      Pro-2: Summary of Programs in the Division of Medical Education, Exhibit I, Presented at Rockefeller Foundation Board Meeting; May 23, 1929
      Pro-3 DR 375: Summary of Report of the Special Committee on the Division of Medical Education; November 9, 1928
      Pro-4: The Rockefeller Foundation Quarterly Bulletin, Vol. V, No. 2; October 1931
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-5 - Pro-7, 7a, 7b, Pro-8 - Pro-12, 1928-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Pro-5: Ruby Hayes; Transfer of Work of China Medical Board to Medical Sciences Memorandum; 1928
      Pro-6: Richard M. Pearce; Past and Future Programs; January 15, 1930
      Pro-7: History and Future Program, Extract from Agenda for Special Trustees Meeting (Complete agenda filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-23); April 11, 1933
      Pro-7b: Warren Weaver; The Science of Man; November 29, 1933
      Pro-8 DR 475: The Medical and Natural Sciences Cooperative Program, extract from Interim Report of Activities Presented to Trustees (complete Report filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-24); December 13, 1933
      Pro-9 DR 486: Extract from Report of Committee on Appraisal and Plan Presented at Trustees Meeting (complete Report filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-27); December 11, 1934
      Pro-10 DR 500: The Medical Science Budget, Extract from the Director's Report on Program (complete Report filed 3.1 900 Pro-28); December 11, 1935
      Pro-11: Extract from Statement of Program Presented at Special Trustees Conference (complete report filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-30); December 15, 1936
      Pro-12: Dr. Alan Gregg, Warren Weaver, Dr. Wilbur A. Sawyer; Some Promising Fields for Foundation Activity Compiled by Officers of the Rockefeller Foundation, Opportunities for Foundation Activity in Medical and Natural Sciences and Public Health; 1938
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-13 - Pro-18, 1942-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Pro-13: Analysis of Program in Relation to Changing World Conditions Preliminary Divisional Statement used at Officers Conference (complete Report filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-35); October 7, 1942
      Pro-14:
      Pro-15: Grants Affected by War Activities; 1941
      Pro-16: Excerpt from Plans for Future Work of the Rockefeller Foundation, November 1944, Used as a Basis for Discussion at Trustees Meeting (Complete Report filed RG 3.1 900 Pro-40, see also RG 3.1 900 Pro-40a); April 4, 1945
      Pro-17: Dr. Alan Gregg; A Program in the Medical Sciences; April 1, 1950
      Pro-18: Extract form Report of the Rockefeller Foundation, Commission on Review of the International Health Division (Complete Report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro CR-9); November 1951
    - Program and Policy - Bulletins and Reprints, 1919-1931 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Program and Policy - Full Time System, 1914-1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Program and Policy - Full Time System, 1914-1948 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Program and Policy - Legal Medicine, 1925, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Program and Policy - Medical Libraries, 1921-1926 (1957) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Program and Policy - Nursing Education, 1917-1932 (1950) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Program and Policy - Nursing Education - Reports - Pro Nurs-1, Nurs-2, 1920-1925 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Pro Nurs-1: Conference on Training of Nurses Called by Officers of the Rockefeller Foundation, Hotel Commodore, New York, New York; February 28, 1920
      Pro Nurs-2: Report of Conference on Nursing Education; October 5, 1925
    - Program and Policy - Psychiatry, 1916-1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Program and Policy - Psychiatry, 1916-1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Program and Policy - Psychiatry - Reports - Pro Psy-1 - Pro Psy-6, 1930-1941 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Pro Psy-1: Medical Sciences- Psychology, Excerpt from Princeton Conference Report; October 1930
      Pro Psy-1a: Dean David L. Edsall; Mental Health Memorandum Regarding Possible Psychiatric Developments; October 3, 1930
      Pro Psy-1b: Alan Gregg; Memorandum Regarding Program in the Field of Human Personality; March 17, 1932
      Pro Psy-2 DR 469: Excerpt from Agenda for Rockefeller Foundation Meeting; April 13, 1933
      Pro Psy-3 DR 475: Excerpt from 1933 Interim Report to Trustees Meeting; December 13, 1933
      Pro Psy-4 DR 486: Excerpt from Report of Appraisal Committee; December 11, 1934
      Pro Psy-5 DR 500: Excerpt from Director's Report on Program, Part of Agenda for Trustees Meeting; December 11, 1935
      Pro Psy-6 DR 582: Alan Gregg; What is Psychiatry?; December 3, 1941
    - Program and Policy - Psychiatry - Reports - Pro Psy-7, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Pro Psy-7: Robert S. Morison; Exploration of Proposal to Supply Circuit Riders in Neurology to Various Schools; June 25, 1945
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Teaching, 1923-1947 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Teaching, 1923-1947 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Program and Policy - Sex Research, 1935-1937 (1948) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Program and Policy - Sex Research - Reports - Pro Sex-1 - Pro Sex-3, 1933-1937 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Pro Sex-1 DR 469: Agenda for Special Meeting; April 11, 1933
      Pro Sex-2 DR 475: Interim Report of Activities of the Rockefeller Foundation During 1933; 1933
      Pro Sex-3: Raymond B. Fosdick; Relations Between the Medical Sciences and Natural Sciences Statement of Policy Presented at Executive Session of Trustees, November 30, 1937; December 10, 1937
    - Program and Policy - Sex Research - Reports - Pro Sex-4, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Pro Sex-4: Research Problems of Sex (Excerpt from Trustees' Confidential Bulletin); December 1949
    - Program and Policy - Veterinary Medicine, 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Program and Policy - Veterinary Medicine - Report - Pro Vet-1, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Pro Vet-1: Report on Veterinary Work in Europe; 1928
    - Program and Policy - Virus Diseases, 1930-1936 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Common Room, 1927-1948; 907; 1 document case
    Correspondence and leases regarding the officers' dining rooms in the RAC and Time-Life buildings.
    - Common Room, 1928-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Common Room, 1928-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Common Room, 1928-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Common Room - Reports - Com-1, Com-2, 1927-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Com-1: Analysis of Common Room Accounts, Rockefeller Foundation; September 22, 1927
      Com-2: Common Room; May 1, 1927-June 30, 1933
    - Interboard Relations, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Health Division, 1902-1973; 908; 27 document cases
    Correspondence, memoranda and reports relating to program and policy in this field. Material concerning predecessors of this division, i.e. the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission, the International Health Commission, and the International Health Board, can also be found here. Of special interest is a large selection of correspondence, notes and drafts concerning the history of the International Health Division.
    SEE ALSO: Separate Rockefeller Sanitary Commission collection SEE ALSO: R.G. 5, International Health Board/Division
    - Funds - (Minutes), 1917-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Funds - (Minutes), 1917-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Funds - (Minutes), 1917-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Funds, 1917-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Funds, 1917-1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Funds, 1917-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - History - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - History - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - History - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18.01)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18.02)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18.03)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18.04)
    - History - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18.05)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.06)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.07)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.08)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.09)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.1)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.11)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.12)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.13)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.14)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.15)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.16)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.17)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.06)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.07)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.08)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.09)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.1)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.11)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.12)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.13)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.14)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.15)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.16)
    - History - Correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 002A, Folder 18.17)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Volumes 1-2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Volumes 1-2 (Box 3, Folder 19.01)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Volume 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Malaria (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Public Health (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Rockefeller Foundation Health Commission (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Source Material (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Typhus (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Notes - Yellow Fever (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 1, "Introduction" (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 2, The Isolationist Period (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 3, The Roots of the International Health Commission (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 4, Launching (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 5, Running Start (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 6, Wickliffe Rose (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 7, Accent on Research (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 8, International Health Division and the War (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 9, George K. Strode (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Manuscript - Chapter 10, Lab and Field (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - History - Lewis Hackett Draft Notes (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Agriculture Sciences (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - American Association of Fund-Raising Counsel (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Appendix A (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - "Author's Note" (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - A (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Balfour, Marshall C. (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Barlow, Claude Herman (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Beeuwkes, Henry (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Bevier, George (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Brazil (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Bugher, John C. (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - Buttrick, Wallace (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - History - Greer Williams' Notes - B (Box 6, Folder 52)